Finding Aid for the Republic Pictures Corporation Records LSC.0979
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Shooting Scripts
  - Twilight on the Rio Grande [1602]; sw: Dorrell and Stuart E. McGowan; series: Supreme Deluxe. (Box 100)
  - UnClaimed Cargo [1262].; sw: Albert DeMond; series: Variety., 1951 (Box 112)
  - Under California Stars [1621].; sw: Paul Gangelin, Sloan Nibley; series: Premiere Trucolor., 1947 (Box 103)
  - Under Colorado Skies [1677].; sw: Louise Rousseau; series: All Star., 1947 (Box 121)
  - The Undercover Woman [1272].; sw: Jerry Sackheim, Sherman Lowe; series: Jubilee., 1945 (Box 118)
  - Under Mexicali Stars [1803].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Paramount Western., 1950 (Box 108)
  - Under Nevada skies [1429].; sw: Paul Gangelin and J. Bonton Cheney; series: Roy Rogers Premiere., 1946 (Box 105, 13877)
  - Under Texas Skies [1015].; series: Mesquiteers., 1940 (Box 133)
  - The Uninvited Guest [1484].; sw: Milton Gunzburg; series: Deluxe., 1946 (Box 107)
  - Union Pacific Scouts [1435].; sw: Bennett Cohen, Betty Burbridge; series: Superior., 1945 (Box 106)
  - Unmasked [1744].; sw: Albert DeMond, Norman S. Hall; series: Variety., 1949 (Box 63)
  - Untamed Heiress [6033].; sw: Barry Shipman., 1953 (Box 130)
  - Utah [1329].; sw: Jack Townley, John K. Butler; series: Rogers premiere., 1944 (Box 120)
  - Utah Wagon Train [1809].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Paramount., 1951 (Box 109)
  - Valley of the Wild Stallion [1819].; sw: Gerald Geraghty; series: Paramount-Rex Allen., 1953 (Box 119)
  - Valley of the Zombies [1560].; sw: Dorrell and Stuart E. McGowan; series: Jubilee., 1945 (Box 106)
  - The Vampire's Ghost [1471].; sw: John K. Butler, Leigh Brackett; series: Jubilee., 1944 (Box 103)
  - The Vanishing Westerner [1693].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Action Western., 1949 (Box 63)
  - Vigilante Hideout [1731].; sw: Richard Wormser; series: Famous Western., 1950 (Box 62)
  - Vigilantes of Boom Town [1614].; sw: Earle Snell; series: Red Ryder., 1946 (Box ?)
  - Vigilantes of Dodge City [1414].; sw: Norman S. Hall; series: Red Ryder Western., 1944 (Box 103, 111)
  - Village Barn Dance [979]., 1939. (Box 90)
  - Wagon Tracks West [1305]., 1943. (Box 118)
  - Wagons Westward [966]., 1940. (Box 113)
  - Wagon Wheels Westward [1515].; sw: Earle Snell; series: Red Ryder Western., 1945 (Box 102)
  - Washington Cowboy [704]., 1938. (Box 71)
  - The Wayward Girl [2041].; sw: Houston Branch., 1956 (Box 130)
  - Web of Danger [1584].; sw: M.M. Raison, David Lang; series: Variety., 1946 (Box 107)
  - Wells Fargo Gunmaster [1736].; sw: M. Coates Webster; series: Famous Western., 1951 (Box 77)
  - We're on the Air [?].; sw: Bradford Ropes., 1936 (Box 72)
  - West of Cimarron [1114].; series: Mesquiteer., 1941 (Box 66)
  - Western Affair [1979].; sw: Andrew Solt; series: Deluxe., 1954 (Box 85)
  - Western Jamboree [804].; series: Autry., 1938 (Box 128)
  - Westward Ho [1117].; series: Mesquiteers., 1942 (Box 65)
  - Whispering Footsteps [1243]., 1943. (Box 120)
  - Who Killed Aunt Maggie? [1037]., 1940. (Box 133)
  - The Wild Frontier [1711].; sw: Albert DeMond; series: Famous Western., 1947 (Box 88)
  - Wild Horse Rodeo [713]., 1938. (Box 88)
  - Wings Across the Pacific [1904].; sw: Richard Tregaskis; series: Deluxe., 1951 (Box 83)
  - Without a Net [732]., n.d. (Box 82)
  - Wolf of New York [955]., 1939. (Box 89)
  - Women in War [983]., 1940. (Box 70)
  - The Woman They Almost Lynched [1944].; sw: John Meredyth Luoas; series: Deluxe., 1951 (Box 94, 115)
  - Women from Headquarters [1785].; sw: Gene Lewis; series: Variety., 1950 (Box 102)
  - Wyoming [1575].; sw: Lawrence Hazard and Richard Wormser; series: Deluxe., 1946 (Box 123)
  - The Wyoming Bandit [1724].; sw: M. Coates Webster; series: Famous Westerns., 1949 (Box 72)
  - X Marks the Spot [1154]., 1942. (Box 92)
  - The Yellow Rose of Texas [1322].; sw: Jack Townley., 1944 (Box 90)
  - Yokel Boy, [1081]., 1941. (Box 120)
  - Young Bill Hickok [1022]., 1940. (Box 136)
  - Young Buffalo Bill [924]., 1939. (Box 113)
  - Zanazbuku [?]., 1955. (Box 129)